<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Aporime Technologies</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Aporime Technologies</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>About Us</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>APORIME TECHNOLOGIES Aporime Technologies is founded by a group of highly experienced software engineers and enterprise architects who are specialized in the following areas:
 Optimizations 3D graphics including VR and AR Multi-platform video game porting Scalable web architecture  OUR EXPERIENCES Before starting Aporime Technologies, we built highly scalable web services that have been serving the world&amp;rsquo;s biggest e-commerce companies, such as Walmart, Costco, FedEx, CVS, Staples, Sam&amp;rsquo;s Club and Quill.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Citizens of Earth</title>
      <link>/project/citizens-of-earth/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/citizens-of-earth/</guid>
      <description>This project was a classic game rendering engine porting work for a client who needed a skilled rendering engineers who can deliver multi-platform 3D engines in under tight deadlines.
Quick Facts  Client: Eden Industries Publisher: Atlus Type: Game Porting Length: 2 Months Platforms: PS4, Wii U, PS Vita, Nintendo 3DS  Background When Eden Industries signed multi-platform deal with Atlus, the founder of Eden Industries, Ryan, quickly realized that he needs a rendering specialist who can port his in-house OpenGL rendering engine to 4 different game consoles.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/contact/</guid>
      <description> We are here to help you Got any hard tech problem you cannot solve? Drop us a message. Just fill out the form below and we&amp;rsquo;ll get back to you as soon as possible (usually within two business days).
Loading... </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Metro Sudoku Privacy Policy</title>
      <link>/privacy-policy/metro-sudoku/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/privacy-policy/metro-sudoku/</guid>
      <description>Privacy Policy Aporime Technologies Inc built the Metro Sudoku app as an Ad Supported app. This SERVICE is provided by Aporime Technologies Inc at no cost and is intended for use as is.
This page is used to inform visitors regarding our policies with the collection, use, and disclosure of Personal Information if anyone decided to use our Service.
If you choose to use our Service, then you agree to the collection and use of information in relation to this policy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What&#39;s for Lunch Privacy Policy</title>
      <link>/privacy-policy/whats-for-lunch/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/privacy-policy/whats-for-lunch/</guid>
      <description>Privacy Policy Aporime Technologies Inc built the What&amp;rsquo;s for Lunch app as an Ad Supported app. This SERVICE is provided by Aporime Technologies Inc at no cost and is intended for use as is.
This page is used to inform visitors regarding our policies with the collection, use, and disclosure of Personal Information if anyone decided to use our Service.
If you choose to use our Service, then you agree to the collection and use of information in relation to this policy.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>